This is the kind of question here Brij Dham has
made a target, if you talk about sandwich then there is
internet here at all, despite this they have
increased the target to eight thousand rupees per share,
they believe that whatever is less and those who have
come from Majnu have performed very well,
Morgan Stanley's target is
₹2000 and
subscribe, what is their ghazal, there is a contra on this, they have
increased them to 60 60 60
and if you are expecting better results than expected then
perhaps you should
subscribe to the report of the facial and if you are going to buy,
look at the cute basis, management and strong
exception have shown and even now
tell me the salary, due to that there is employment, as far as the
commentary on the stock is concerned,
I have said it was good and as far as the
company is concerned,
despite their valuation being expensive, some people
feel that due to that they are giving up on the company,
Jhaal Jhaal